let questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "What is Katniss's sister's full name?",
    answer: "Primrose",
    options: ["Pamela", "Primly", "Prim", "Primrose"],
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "How did Katniss's father die?",
    answer: "In a mine explosion",
    options: [
      "In a hunting accident",
      "In a mine explosion",
      "He got trapped in a collapsed mine",
      "He was murdered by the Capitol",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "At what skill is Gale better than Katniss?",
    answer: "Setting snares",
    options: ["Setting snares", "Using an axe", "Swimming", "Bird calls"],
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Who gives Katniss the mockingjay pin?",
    answer: "Madge",
    options: ["Gale", "Cinna", "Madge", "Prim"],
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: "Why does the Capitol hold the Hunger Games?",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "As a way to control the size of the population",
      "To keep the districts happy",
      "Because they are part of a religious festival",
      "To remind the districts that they are powerless against it",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "Which word best describes Haymitch?",
    answer: "Gruff",
    options: ["Sensitive", "Polite", "Silly", "Gruff"],
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "Under what circumstances did Katniss first meet Peeta?",
    answer: "Katniss was looking for food and Peeta gave her bread",
    options: [
      "Katniss was looking for food and Peeta gave her bread",
      "They were both in the woods hunting",
      "They did a project at school together",
      "Peeta was injured and Katniss's mother helped himt",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Why does the Capitol hold the Hunger Games?",
    answer: "To remind the districts that they are powerless against it",
    options: [
      "As a way to control the size of the population",
      "To keep the districts happy",
      "Because they are part of a religious festival",
      "To remind the districts that they are powerless against it",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question:
      "What does Katniss think when she first sees the residents of the Capitol?",
    answer: "They are superficial and ridiculous",
    options: [
      "They are sophisticated and beautiful",
      "They are superficial and ridiculous",
      "They are overweight and tall",
      "They are ungroomed and slovenly",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "Who or what is Katniss named after?",
    answer: "A plant with edible roots",
    options: [
      "Her grandmother",
      "A plant with edible roots",
      "A type of bird",
      "Catnip",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 11,
    question: "What are tesserae?",
    answer: "Extra rations of grain and oil",
    options: [
      "Extra rations of grain and oil",
      "Hybrid animals created by the Capitol",
      "A type of plant",
      "What the children are called who are chosen to compete in the Games",
    ],
  },
  {
    number: 12,
    question: "Which training station does Peeta excel at?",
    answer: "Camouflage",
    options: ["Archery", "Knife throwing", "Camouflage", "knot tying"],
  },
];
